Guide to the Project Maje Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Videocassettes, 1980-2005; Series XI
  - State Law and Order Restoration Council human rights abuses, circa 1988 - circa 1997; 1 (Box 99)
  - Don't Fence Me In: Major Marry and the Karen Refugees from Burma, 2004; 1 (Box 100)
  - No Childhood at all: Child soldiers in Burma, 1997; 1 (Box 101)
  - In the Shadow of the Pagodas: The Other Burma, 2004; 1 (Box 102)
  - Visit to Wa documentary (A&E), 2002; 1 (Box 103)
  - Burma Rough Cut, undated; 1 (Box 104)
  - Burma Senate demonstrations raw footage, undated; 1 (Box 105)
  - Free Burma Coalition, undated; 1 (Box 106)
  - Rubies in the Golden Triangle, undated; 1 (Box 107)
  - CSPAN-2 Book Discussion with Alan Rabinowitz, "Beyond the Last Village", 2002; 1 (Box 108)
    The second half of the videocassette recording is a Survivor television show episode.
  - "How Many Strikes Do Big Corporations Get", National Lawyers Guild, 1999; 1 (Box 109)
  - NBC Heroin in Burma, undated; 1 (Box 110)
  - Burmese music and information on Jewish chins, undated; 1 (Box 111)
  - Nightline special on UNOCAL, 2005 May 5; 1 (Box 112)
    The Nightline program ends abrubtly at the 1 hour and 1 minute mark, the rest of the recording consists of other TV programs.
  - National Coalition Government Union of Burma, undated; 1 (Box 113)
  - The Water Hyacinth, undated; 1 (Box 114)